
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="motivational_quotes">
        <item>Pain is just weakness leaving your body. Sweat it out.</item>
        <item>If it doesn\'t challenge you, it doesn\'t change you.</item>
        <item>Sore today, strong tomorrow. No shortcuts.</item>
        <item>Your muscles don\'t care how tired you are. Lift anyway.</item>
        <item>Burn the fat, build the muscle, earn the crown.</item>
        <item>The only bad workout is the one that didn\'t happen.</item>
        <item>Blood, sweat, and respect. First two you give, last one you earn.</item>
        <item>Fall in love with the burn. That\'s where the magic happens.</item>
        <item>Comfort zones build nothing. Push past the breaking point.</item>
        <item>Temporary pain brings permanent pride.</item>
        <item>Heavy weights, high standards, zero excuses.</item>
        <item>Turn your excuses into fuel.</item>
        <item>Strong core, soft curves, unbreakable spirit.</item>
        <item>You don\'t have to choose between power and grace. Claim both.</item>
        <item>Carve your body like a sculptor shapes marble. Every rep matters.</item>
        <item>Build a chest of steel and a waist like art.</item>
        <item>True strength bends, adapts, and conquers.</item>
        <item>Fierce in your discipline, stunning in your design.</item>
        <item>Be your own architect. Design the reflection you want to see.</item>
        <item>A tight waist and a fierce mindset—that\'s elite control.</item>
        <item>Motivation gets you started. Discipline keeps you going.</item>
        <item>Do it when you don\'t feel like it. Especially then.</item>
        <item>Small daily improvements over time lead to stunning results.</item>
        <item>Win the morning, win the workout, win the day.</item>
        <item>Consistency beats intensity when intensity is inconsistent.</item>
        <item>Your future self is begging you not to quit today.</item>
        <item>Grind in silence. Let the mirror do the talking.</item>
        <item>Show up for yourself, even when nobody is watching.</item>
        <item>Excellence is not a singular act; it\'s a daily habit.</item>
        <item>No zero days. Do at least one thing toward your goal today.</item>
        <item>You are stronger than your excuses. Period.</item>
        <item>Doubt kills more dreams than failure ever will.</item>
        <item>Fall down seven times, stand up eight, stronger each time.</item>
        <item>Your mind will quit a hundred times before your body does. Make your mind obey.</item>
        <item>Fear is a liar. Push past it.</item>
        <item>Be addicted to bettering yourself.</item>
        <item>Unstoppable is a choice, not a trait.</item>
        <item>Pressure makes diamonds. Keep the pressure on.</item>
        <item>Earn your mirror.</item>
        <item>Outwork yesterday.</item>
        <item>Sweat now, shine later.</item>
        <item>Build the beast. Shape the beauty.</item>
        <item>Zero regrets. 100% effort.</item>
        <item>Focus. Execute. Evolve.</item>
        <item>Steel your core.</item>
        <item>Stop wishing, start lifting.</item>
        <item>Stay hungry. Stay relentless.</item>
        <item>Sculpt your masterpiece.</item>
        <item>Train hard, stay humble.</item>
        <item>Dominate your routine.</item>
        <item>No gym? No problem. The floor is your dojo.</item>
        <item>A room, a band, and a dream are all it takes.</item>
        <item>Home is where the real discipline is forged.</item>
        <item>Gravity is your heaviest weight. Master it.</item>
        <item>Every rep in this room is a step toward freedom.</item>
        <item>One more set. One more rep. That\'s where champions are made.</item>
        <item>Your body can do it. Now convince your brain.</item>
        <item>Look in the mirror. That\'s your only competition.</item>
        <item>Keep your head high and your core tight.</item>
        <item>You are writing your own story with every drop of sweat.</item>
        <item>Unstoppable starts right now.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
